playtoongames.com 2017-05-20

# Play Toon Games - Cartoon games | Ben 10 Games | Free Online Games

* * *

Play Toon Games is committed to providing an entertaining, fun and educational service. Play Toon Games.com is a property of Play Toon Games Limited "Play Toon Games". Play Toon Games respects the privacy concerns of visitors to Play Toon Games.com. Play Toon Games does not target its website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13. We take measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity.   

We may log IP addresses and/or drop cookies to prevent abuse of our website and/or to enhance services. Email addresses of under 13 year olds are not stored. They are encrypted into an unrecoverable format using a one way hash.  

We have an internal notification system to communicate with under 13 players and do not send them emails. We do not retain any personal information beyond the time it is needed. We may use information to ensure that users are compliance with our terms. Over 13's may authorize and receive email notifications related to Play Toon Games services. Play Toon Games Limited may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Play Toon Games's property, visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.   

We may sometimes use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors' experience or to offer products, programs, and services. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services.  

Our site may place a small file, called a cookie, on your hard drive to provide you with a better website. A cookie does not, in any way, give us access to your computer or to any personally identifiable information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. It only helps us analyze web traffic or lets web applications respond to you as an individual. Our authorized third-party advertisers in the course of serving ads to you, may also place cookies on your browser or use tracking technology to collect information. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser's settings section. Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a DART cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  

Play Toon Games does not require under 13's to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity as a condition of participation.  

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.  

To protect your child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your child.  

This Privacy Policy is part of the Play Toon Games main Terms and Conditions which you agree to by accessing the Play Toon Games.com webstie and/or services. You agree that Play Toon Games Limited may change this Privacy Policy and the main Play Toon Games Terms and Conditions at any time.  

Play Toon Games recommends that Parents take time to communicate and educate their children about Internet Safety.
